$89,000
profit this month selling put options
with a win rate of 89%
and the month is not even done yet. We
still have one more week to go. In this
video, I'm going to show you how I sell
put options to generate a consistent
monthly income. This is a simple
strategy, but most people still don't
know how to do it the right way. So, if
you want to learn how to make a monthly
income by selling put options, you want
to watch this video till the end. I can
refresh this page to show you that this
is an actual platform and I can also go
over all these charts and you we can
also go over some of my trades and you
can see that this is not something like
Photoshop. This is a real trading
platform. I also verify my results using
a third-party platform called Kinfo.
Here you can see that in the last 1 year
I made $420,000
in verified profits. Selling puts is one
of the simplest and most effective
trading strategy because in this we can
win even if we are wrong on the
direction, we can win without day
trading, without a lot of screen time,
and we get paid up front when we make
the trade and I have 90% win rate on the
strategy. I will show you step-by-step
on how I build my monthly income engine,
how I find high probability trade
setups, how to execute and manage the
trades in the trading platform, and how
the math makes money behind the
strategy. If you stay till the end, I
will show you my real trade breakdowns
where the stock went down by 40 to 50%
and how I still turn those trades into
profit. This video is for education
only. I'm not a licensed financial
advisor. Any ideas I share in this video
are for examples only. Talk to your
financial advisor or do your own
research before making any decisions.
Here is how the strategy actually works.
The reason why the reason why the
strategy is so effective is because
there can be four scenarios in the
market. The market can go up, stay flat,
or go down a little, or it can crash
hard. Now, you can see that in three out
of four scenarios, we win. As long as
the stock stays above, goes up, or goes
down a little, we are going to win. But,
if we have a big market crash, in that
case, temporarily, I'm going to lose,
but in long term, I can still recover
from the trade and come back in the
green. And I'm going to show you some
example of that as well. The way this
strategy works is let's say a stock like
Nvidia is right now trading at $208, and
I think that over the next month, I
expect the stock to go up, or at least
hold a certain level. Now, if I think
that Nvidia can stay above $200 over the
next month, I can go out and sell a put
option at 200 strike, and I will get
paid a credit for it. When I sell a put
option at 200 strike, as long as the
stock holds this line over the next
month, I'm going to win. So, if I go out
and I sell at 200 strike put for October
2nd expiration, which is about 39 days,
I will get $677
credit up front for it. This basically
means that I'm selling an insurance to
someone with a promise that I agree to
buy 100 shares of this stock at 200
price by the given expiration date. Now,
at the expiration date, if the stock is
above $200, nobody would want to sell me
shares at a discounted price. In that
case, this option is going to expire
worthless, and I get to keep $677
as profit. But, if the stock is under
$200 at expiration, then I will have to
buy 100 shares of this stock at $200,
but I still get to keep this credit,
which is going to offset my cost basis.
So, instead of paying $20,000, my net
cost is going to be about 19,332,
which will set my cost basis and break
even price at $193.23.
So, in that case, that is going to give
me 7.3%
downside protection. So, that means as
long as the stock trades over $193 till
October 2nd, I can make some profit. If
the stock is above $200, I make the full
$677
profit. This is kind of like earning a
rental income, but when things go
against us, we have an option to buy
shares, and then we can turn around and
sell covered calls against it. And I'm
going to show you an example of a trade
like that in this video. So,
theoretically, we have about 72% chance
of making profit in this trade. Now,
there are three ways to sell put option.
One is that you sell a cash secured put.
In that case, I need about $20,000 to
make a trade like this. That means if I
win this trade, I'm going to make 3.5%
return on capital if the stock stays
flat. But if the stock moves up fast, I
can capture most of my profit within a
couple of weeks. So, that can produce a
higher annualized return. And the second
option is to sell using portfolio
secured margin. In that case, I only
need about $3,320
to make a trade like this. And in that
case, I will make about 20% return on my
margin. But this is But selling on
margin is also high risk. It is not for
newbie. If you're newbie, you want to
sell either cash secured put, or you can
also sell a put spread where you can
make a trade like this with just a few
hundred dollars. To do that, you're
basically going to sell a 200 strike
put, and then you can buy a put at a
lower strike. So, let's say I buy 190
strike put to hedge my position. So, in
that case, I can make a trade like this
with just $695, where my upside can be
$305,
which is about 31%. So, this is much
more capital efficient. And in this
trade, as long as the stock stays up And
in this trade, as long as the stock
stays above $200, I win this trade, and
I I to keep this full credit. I made a
lot of trades like this over the last
couple of months and I posted most of
them in my Discord channel. And here you
can see that almost all the trades were
like consistent winners. You can join my
Discord using the link in the
description below. But if you really
want to be successful, you can't just do
that by copying somebody else's trades.
If you don't know what you're doing, you
cannot have a conviction in a trade. To
do that, you need to understand the
strategies on how to fish for yourself,
how to make your own trades, and how to
manage trades when things go against
you. How you can roll and adjust your
way out of losing trades and turn them
into break even and winners. I'm going
to show you some example breakdowns, but
if you want to learn the full process,
then check out my coaching program in
the description below. In the coaching
program, I teach you my income
generation strategies, delta neutral
strategies, so we can make trades
without relying on the market direction,
rolling and adjustments, what to do when
things go against you. And I also give
you my screeners and back test, which
you can use to systematically make your
trades. And when you sign up for the
coaching program, you also get access to
the Discord membership included in it.
You can join using the link in the
description below. To find high
probability option selling
opportunities, I like to use the Moomoo
trading platform because in their mobile
app, they have a very powerful feature
called option selling dashboard. So,
let's go to the Moomoo mobile app. Here
I can go to markets and then options and
I will scroll down a little bit to find
the seller dashboard. Now, if I go to
the seller dashboard, there are two
options here, cash secured put and
covered call. So, I'll go to cash
secured put. Now, this tool is going to
show me some lucrative opportunities to
sell put options, so I can go to filters
to set my criteria. Now, I'm sharing my
own criteria, but feel free to modify
and set up criteria that works for your
risk profile. So, I'll set up market cap
at $1 billion and then go down and and
select days to expiration at 28 to 60
DTE. So, that means I will mostly get
opportunities where the days to
expiration is about 4 to 8 weeks. And
then go down and set the OTM probability
to 70%. That means it will only show me
trade opportunities where I can have
more than 70% probability of profit. And
then go down. And here I want at least
24% annualized ROI on cash secured put.
So, if I'm selling a put option with 1
month expiration, it will typically at
least have 2% return on cash. Now, if
you're using margin or put spread, then
of course it is going to be much higher.
But this is my minimum baseline that I
want to set. And then save. Now, it is
going to show you a lot of different
option contracts. Uh
here it is showing individual option
contracts with expiration dates and
strikes. And you can pick and choose
what you like. We can also go here and
sort it by annualized ROI high to low so
that it is showing the highest so that
it is showing the highest ROI
opportunities first. If I see a ticker
which I don't know about, which I don't
want to own, I'm not going to trade it.
I only want to focus on stocks which I
would like to own because the goal is
that we collect premiums month after
month. But if we have a bad month, then
we get shares assigned, then we hold the
shares and run the wheel strategy. So,
don't just chase the high ROI. You want
to chase high quality with high ROI. And
here we can also go back and set it to
market cap $10 billion so that it is
only going to show us large cap and
ETFs. Now, here we see SOXL ETF, which
is a 3x leverage ETFs on semiconductors.
Now, leverage ETFs like SOXL, TECL,
TQQQ, they offer a very high ROI. You
can easily make 5% or more in a month
and it can work really well if you are
comfortable holding that ETF because
when it comes to draw downs leverage
ETFs can be double edge sword. They can
go up a lot but they can also go down a
lot. So you want to focus on tickers
which you would like to own. If you want
to have a leverage ETF in your portfolio
then that is something you want you can
consider. Now here I see Nebius which
looks interesting to me. Nebius stock
went up a lot recently and then it came
back down. It had a good earnings and
now it looks like it is in consolidation
again. So here it is suggesting that we
can sell 175 strike put for September 25
expiration which is about 32 days. I can
get about $727
premium for it. You ideally want to look
at stocks which you would like to own.
If this is not a stock you would like to
own then this is not for you. You can
keep moving on and find something you
like. Let's look at its chart. So here
we can see that it is in a long term
uptrend but lately it has had a pullback
with all of the AI related stocks and it
had a big run up on earnings and now it
has it is now back down to the point
where it was before earnings. So if we
can sell 175 put which is going to be
about this level. Last month when all of
the AI and semiconductor stocks were
dumping this stock put in a bottom at
150. So here if you are selling 175
strike it is actually pretty close to
that bottom. So if I want to if I'm not
comfortable at 175 I can even consider
selling at 150. In that case worst case
scenario if the trade goes against me I
will get shares assigned at 150. So now
let's model this in Option Strat. Here
we can see that 175 put will get a $727
credit and it will set the break even
price at $167
which is 20% downside protection. That
means stock can go up it can go sideways
and I can still make profit as long as
it stays above $168. Now, if I want to
push my break-even point down to 150, I
can reduce the strike price. But in that
case, I'm only going to get 277 credit,
but I will have higher chance of profit.
So, it is up to you how you want to set
it up. There are a lot of possibilities.
For me personally,
I like to go for somewhere between 20
delta to 30 delta. So, if I'm selling 20
delta put, it is going to be at 175
strike. Here, I can make 4.3% return on
cash-secured put. And if I'm using
margin, my margin is only going to be
couple thousand dollars. And in that
case, I'm getting $727 credit. But you
can also convert it into a put spread.
To do that, all you have to do is buy
another put, which can be 10 to 20
points below the short strike. So, in
that case, I can make 26% return on
investment with a 78% chance of profit.
So, this this is my ideal setup. I like
to select delta between 20 to 30 delta
with 4 to 8 weeks expiration. And if the
trade starts to work my way, I can start
taking profit at 40 to 50% and by the
time it makes 70 to 80% profit, I can
close most of my position. Now, at what
level I take profit can be sometimes
subjective because it is time-weighted.
So, if I enter a trade with 6 weeks
expiration, and in week one or week two,
it makes 40% profit, I'm very happy with
it because now I'm instead of waiting
for 6 weeks, I'm able to capture half
the profit in just one or two weeks.
That makes my much higher annualized
return. And then I can move on to my
next trade. And also sometimes when a
trade runs up fast, chances are that it
may not go straight up. It can go up 50%
then come back down. In that case, I can
re-enter the same trade again and get in
and out of the same trade couple of
times and capture even higher profit.
Now, while selecting Delta, if you
select Delta, which is you are going to
have a higher win rate. With higher
Delta, you are going to have lower win
rate. Some people go way out of the
money and try to sell five or 10 Delta
put. With that, you will have 90% win
rate, but your wins are going to be much
smaller. And when you lose, your losses
are going to be bigger. And when I do 20
to 30 Delta, that is usually the sweet
spot where I can have 80 to 90% win
rate. But when the trade goes against
me, I'm getting it at a substantially
lower cost basis that either I can roll
or take an assignment and then work my
way out of it. Now, what is the best
time to sell put? I like to sell puts
when implied volatility is high because
that's when we get more downside
protection, we get higher premiums, and
the trade will have higher chance of
making profit fast. So, I like to look
at these three parameters. The first is
VIX. VIX should be between 15 to 30
because when it's less than 15, at that
point, the premiums are too low. They
are not pricing in the risk. When the
VIX is more than 30,
in that scenario, the market is in a
panic mode. In that case, instead of
putting on new trades, I am more focused
on defending my existing positions. That
is the bigger priority for me. And I
want the IV rank to be above 30 and IV
percentile to be above 50. To sell this
put option, I will click the trade
button, then select order type as limit,
and then I can select my limit price
here. So, I'm going to enter 7.5 for now
and then click the sell button, and it
will give you this warning. Just click
continue. And here I can see the order
details and then confirm and submit my
order. To sell cash secured puts, you
need level one options approval. But if
you want to sell portfolio secured puts
using margin, you need level four
options approval. And if you want to
sell put credit spreads, then you need
level three options access. Some brokers
make it very hard to get higher tier
options access and they have very high
capital requirements, but Moomoo has a
very simple process. They just require
$2,000 in assets to apply for level
three options and you need $10,000 to
apply for level four options. The Moomoo
platform is very robust and it has very
powerful features for option traders
including options flow, unusual
activities, zero DT, and option
screeners. They offer commissions free
options trading and when you sign up
using the link in the description below,
you can even get up to $1,000 in welcome
bonus. Thanks to Moomoo for sponsoring
this segment. Now, let's go into the
trade breakdowns. First, I'll go over
easy wins where I just made a trade and
won within a week or two weeks and the
and then we will go into more complex
trades where things went against me,
stock dropped 40 to 50% and I still
turned it into a profit. The first trade
is on Sandisk which I opened on August
of 6. The stock fell down last month and
then it made a floor at $1,000 and that
is where I sold my put option. I sold a
thousand strike put for $7,200
credit. The spot price at that time was
$1,200 and the margin requirement for
this trade was $30,000. So, $7,200
credit on $30,000 margin is really good
and this was an easy win because uh soon
after opening the trade, the stock went
up and I made and this trade was at 60
$800 profit in just 10 days. For cash
secured put, this would be a 7.3% ROI
which is 245%
annualized return, but on margin, this
was a 23% return. I made this trade on
TSM where I sold a 360 strike put for
$900 credit. The spot price at that time
was 410 and soon after opening my trade,
the stock dumped hard and I just held
through my put. I did not need to make
any adjustment because even after this
jump, the stock stayed over my 360
strike price. So, I did not need to do
anything. And then the stock recovered
and my trade made $840 profit in just 90
days, which was about 22% return on
margin. It is 430% annualized return.
And then I made this trade on Coreweave
where the stock had a big crash of 43%
in a couple of weeks and I still turned
this trade into profit. Here is how it
worked. I sold 85 strike port for $530
when the stock was trading at 105. That
means my break-even price would be about
$80, which is about 20% below the spot
price. But then the stock had a big
crash and it went straight through my
strike. On this day, I got 100 shares
assigned with a cost basis of about $80.
And next day the stock went up a little
and then I sold a covered call at 90
strike and I collected additional $720
credit for it, which reduced my cost
basis to $71.8.
So, even though when I entered this
trade, the stock was at 105, I was able
to bring the cost basis down to just
71.8.
At this point, I sold the covered call
for next month expiration, which was
21st of August. So, the stock went lower
after that, but then it had a recovery
leading into the earnings and right
after earnings, it had this pop and it
came back into the $110 range. So, at
that time, I was able to close my shares
and covered call for net $89.2 credit.
So, that means my cost basis was 71.8,
exit was 89.2. That makes a total profit
of $1,740,
which makes 21.8%
return on investment on a fully cash
secured position, which is 162%
annualized. So, even though the stock
went completely against me, I was still
able to turn it around and make a very
big profit. And if you see, the stock is
now back down to 86, but I am already
out with profit. And even in this case,
even if the stock did not go up a lot,
on 21st of August, the stock was near
$90 strike, and I would have still made
about the same amount of profit even in
that scenario. Here is another trade
where the stock went down 52% after my
entry, and I still turned it into profit
using my ruling strategy. I sold 48
strike put on Iron for $310 credit. The
spot price was $60 at the time of entry,
and after that, the stock took like a
straight dump, and it went down to 45.
At that point, I rolled my put down to
45 for additional $18 credit. So, my
total credit at that point received was
3.28, which reduces my breakeven to
41.72.
So, in this case, as long as the stock
holds this $41.7
line, I can still come back into green.
But, the stock went even lower after
that. It went down to $30, but I kept
holding my position because it was not
assigned. So, I held the position, and
after that, the stock recovered after a
couple of weeks. And at that point, when
the stock came back to 45, the trade was
in $173 profit. And a couple of days
after that, this trade was at 48 cent on
the day of expiration with a $280 profit
on one contract. Now, in all these
examples, I'm showing you with one
contract, but I can be trading 10
contracts, 20 contracts, or even 50
contracts in some situations, depending
on the capital requirement for that
trade. If the trade is on a small-size
ticker, then I'm going with more
contracts, but if it is a more expensive
stock, then I'm going with fewer
contracts. Here is another trade where
the stock dropped 42%, and I still
turned it into profit. This trade is on
Marvel, where I sold 220 strike put for
920 credit when the stock was trading at
$280. And soon after my entry, the stock
started dumping just like all the other
tech and semiconductor stocks. And at
that point, I rolled my 220 strike put
to the next month expiration for
September for an additional $850 credit.
So, I received $920 credit to open the
trade, and then I received another $850
credit to roll out my trade to the next
month. So, total credit received was and
that reduces my break-even point to Now,
in this case, if the stock can recover
back to above 202, I can be in profit.
So, after this stock had some recovery
and I was able to close my trade for $6
debit with a net profit of $1,170.
Now, in this case, I was able to turn
profit here even though the stock was
still down 14% from my entry. And you
know what? If I did not roll my trade
here, I would have still made $795
profit on the original expiration date.
Because I sold 220 strike put on the day
of expiration, the spot price for this
stock was $218.
In that case, this trade was actually in
$795 profit. Because I rolled my
position to the next month for
additional credit, I was able to make
more profit than even my initial credit.
If you made it this far, you are on your
way to becoming the top 1% of the
traders. So, if you like this video,
don't forget to hit the like and
subscribe button. And if you have any
questions, post them in the comments and
I will try to answer as many questions
as possible.